# Jia Wen Lee

Software Engineer

# Professional Summary

Software developed that codes and learn skills based on the needs of the task at hand. Worked in high regulatory environments with strict code testing standards as well as a research environment that requires high pace development. 6+ years writing code and building scripts to automate tasks.

# **Employment History**

## Software Engineer, Collins Aerospace, Remote

June 2020 - Present

- Develop, debug, maintain and test software used to run the flight interface and flight managements systems in commercial aircraft in ADA and Python adhering to strict regulatory, safety and testing standards.
- Trained in DO178 B-C

## **Graduate Research Assistant, Iowa State University**

May 2018- June 2020

- Research and develop automation solutions for agriculture tillage.
- Log, process, clean and merge LiDAR data with GPS data and perform post processing data analysis to assess the viability of sensor for client needs.
- Create a GUI using Python QT4 with a back end C++ multi-threaded TCPIP and UDP listener to chart live LiDAR data.

### Co-op, Ag Leader Engineering, Ames, Iowa

May 2017 - Dec 2017

- Optimized existing MATLAB programs used for data processing resulting in a reduction of program run time by a factor of 270. Benchmark time was 9 hours, new program is 2 minutes.
- Create new MATLAB programs and GUI to speed up data processing and data analysis.

### Web Developer, Iowa State University BSE department

October 2015-May 2017

• Program webapps in Javascript, HTML, PHP, and Python to help facilitate research & data collection for Agricultural research

## Education

Iowa State University- Masters of Science in Agriculture Engineering

August 2015 – April 2020

#### **Details**

515-708-8227 jwleehere@gmail.com

#### Links

Website LinkedIn GitHub

### **Accomplishments**

- Made an autonomous snow plow for Ion Autonomous Snowplow Competition
- First Robotics Mentor for Software and Controls
- 2<sup>nd</sup> place in 2016 ASABE Robotics competition

#### **Skills**

Python

JS (electron, react, node)

C++

**ADA** 

SQL

HTML/CSS

Git &SVN

Jama

Jira & Confluence

Agile

PREP

Vista

Debug & Investigate

Software requirements &

testing

Independent Learning

Web Scraping

**CANbus**